[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[theme music playing]
TAKE CHARGE OF MY HEART
[curious music playing]
[Ho-rang gasps]
Oh, no, uh, this isn't what it looks like.
-I, um… -Ah! Ah…
-Huh… -[Bo-bae] No, wait!
[pained gasping]
I swear it's not what it looks like. I… I wasn't…
I wasn't trying to kiss you.
I just woke up, and I was here, and you were right there, and I, uh…
Okay…
-Get out. -Wait! Hang on.
Please…
So when I do this… Nothing.
See? Usually, there's a shock.
It doesn't affect you at all? You don't feel…
-[Ho-rang grunts] -Ah-ah!
I already told you. I really don't like being flirted with like this…
-Flirted with? -[whimsical music playing]
[chuckling] Listen.
I know it sounds like I'm trying to seduce you, but I swear it's not! [sighs]
Gosh, you didn't even bother hearing me out.
And all I've tried to do is explain this whole time…
Go, or I'm calling the cops.
Just hang on!
Look! I had my appendix removed, okay?
This is my hospital room.
This is a single-patient room for VIPs. They always give me this one.
[gasping pointedly] Then why are there two beds?
I just opened my eyes and I was in here.
And I don't care. Now get out.
-[door opens] -[Dr. Jang] Na Bo-bae is right.
[door closes]
You're sharing.
Hello, Doctor.
Oh dear.
-Hm. -[Ho-rang] Let me get this straight.
You're saying the hospital had a blackout,
which is when my artificial heart malfunctioned?
[Dr. Jang] This smart watch displays the remaining charge left on your heart.
Normally, it displays a full charge of 100%.
However, now
it's dropped to 43%.
Then we'll replace it. We can do that.
-You could have more surgery, of course. -Good.
In about three months.
It's too risky to attempt a repeat surgery so soon when you need to recover.
The stress on your body could prove fatal.
And even if everything went smoothly,
you would need extensive rest.
-Full recovery would take at least a year. -That long?
But I… That's impossible. I can't wait that long.
[Dr. Jang] So, for the time being,
your roommate is going to assist us.
-What? -What?
Me? How am I supposed to assist?
I'm at a loss to explain how,
but when you're around, Miss Bo-bae, it's quite remarkable.
Your heart battery gradually recharges.
[electricity fizzing]
This patient, Na Bo-bae, claims she made the power come back on?
Yes.
At first I assumed she was simply nervous before her surgery,
but while we were rolling her down the hall,
the lights there started to flicker.
And, Doctor, look…
-[crackling] -[nurse gasps] Uh…
Her skin, it… it gives off unusually high levels of static electricity.
[watch beeps]
Doctor, it looks like his heart's starting to recharge.
But his heart battery was originally at 6%.
[suspenseful music building]
-[music stops] -Wait, this is…
[intriguing music playing]
[sparks fizzing]
[Dr. Jang] When you're within a ten-meter radius of Miss Bo-bae,
your heart battery charges up, little by little.
[music fades]
-[Dr. Jang grunts] -Goodbye.
Oh no. Wait. Hey, watch out for my stomach. I don't feel good…
You expect me to believe a story like that?
Seriously.
-Ho-rang, wait! -[door closes]
Jeez, why would he just throw me out like that?
[Dr. Jang] Look…
Ho-rang's on edge.
This is his life we're talking about. I don't blame him for not believing me.
To tell you the truth, I barely believe it myself.
But despite all that, I'm convinced that you are his lifeline.
How? You heard him, he doesn't want my help.
Besides, I don't feel like a lifeline. I feel like a piece of string.
You must have noticed there's something weird about me.
Something unusual? How can I help anyone?
Well, we'd have to conduct some more tests to gather more data,
but… but yes, you are unusual.
You know, unusual people can do the most extraordinary things.
Don't be so hard on the piece of string. I bet it can help more than it thinks.
-[pensive music playing] -[Dr. Jang] Hm.
[Ho-rang sighs]
Will you be all right, sir?
Perhaps we should call that woman back to recharge.
[Ho-rang] Don't tell me you believe that.
How can a human recharge an artificial heart?
Three months…
Three months until another surgery?
What will my grandmother say?
And my aunt and Choi Do-yoon are just waiting to take me down.
Plus there's the 30th anniversary, but I still have to sign Ji Eun-ho…
Deep breaths. Breathe, sir.
We can reschedule if we have to.
-What do we do if we can't sign-- -I'll handle it.
I'm gonna make sure to cover every possibility.
[inhales deeply]
Deep breaths…
[exhales slowly]
Have a seat, sir.
[Ho-rang grunting nervously]
-[sighs] -[shoes fall to floor]
[spray spritzes]
-[calming music playing] -[Ho-rang inhales deeply]
[exhales slowly]
-[sighs] -[music stops]
Hey, look, only 1% down!
You sure you'll be all right?
Oh…
Of course. You should really be getting back.
I should, sir. Call me if you need anything else.
Don't let yourself spiral. Try to meditate.
Anxiety and stress will impede your recovery.
Do your best to clear your thoughts, sir.
-[door opens, closes] -[breathing deeply]
[calming music resumes]
-[sighs] -[watch chimes]
[sighs]
[groans softly]
[Dr. Jang] Unusual people can do the most extraordinary things.
Don't be so hard on the piece of string. I bet it can help more than it thinks.
So he has a device in his chest
which is absorbing the current coming from me?
-[scoffs] -[watch chimes]
[intriguing music playing]
[Ho-rang sighs]
What? You kicked me out and now you wanna talk?
Feels a bit desperate, honestly.
Can I please just
borrow you for a minute?
[music ends with a flourish]
[Ho-rang sighs]
[curious music playing]
Ooh, excuse me. What do you think you're doing?
Must be a microchip in there or something…
-Eyes up here, buddy! -[slide whistle plays]
[sighs] If it's not a chip,
what did you do to me?
Are you magic?
I'm not a witch!
I woke up from my surgery and I was next to you. That's it!
All right, fine. We'll just have to chalk it up to a miracle.
My surgery's in three months. I need you with me 'till then.
For the time being, anyway. Till I have another option.
Is that your way of asking? You're bossing me around.
[scoffs]
-[laughs] -You are.
[scoffs] All right, I'll give you what you want.
Wait, what do I want?
[Ho-rang groans softly]
[sighs]
[romantic music playing]
[Bo-bae] Sorry.
Do you think we could give it one more go?
[romantic music builds]
[suspenseful music playing]
Whoa!
[whimsical music playing]
-What are you doing? -What do you mean?
This is what you've wanted ever since we met!
You obviously wanted to kiss me.
That wasn't what I…
That was just…
I just needed to check something… [clears throat]
I don't need to check anything anymore, so we're good.
You have an artificial heart. That's what I felt.
That's all I felt, right?
[clears throat] Oh.
So, what do you want in exchange?
Money?
Money's easy for me.
Name your price.
[snickering]
[sighs] What a guy.
When you didn't know what I wanted, you jumped straight to kissing, wow.
And then you bragged about how much money you could give me,
like it was some kind of charity case.
All you've done from the start is assume.
You could've asked why I followed you after we kissed.
Or why I wanted to know if you felt a spark.
You should've asked!
I wish you'd just asked.
Whatever. I guess your battery charges when I'm around, so fine, I'll help.
I don't want you to die or anything. And that's it. That's all you get.
I don't wanna to be any closer to you than I have to.
[sighs] Great…
[watch chimes]
[intriguing music playing]
[watch bongs]
-[Bo-bae gasps] -[watch chimes]
Hey, what do you think you're doing? Didn't you hear what I told you?
[Ho-rang breaths rapidly]
What? Oh. Hey, let go. Cut it out.
You little… [gasps]
I got a black belt in tae kwon do, you know?
My sister's a tae kwon do gold medalist. She retired, but…
My brother does judo and--
Whoa.
[intriguing music playing]
I just need to check something.
-[sighs] -[watch chimes]
What? I can't believe this!
-[grunts] -[pained groan]
Ah! Ow, my heart.
You were just trying to cop a feel? Tsk!
No…
Ah… ah.
[Ho-rang groans]
[breathing heavily]
It worked.
How could it?
[Dr. Jang] Studies have been conducted on the phenomenon.
Though nothing's been proven, so I can't say for sure.
But the fact remains,
when you're both within a certain distance of each other, your battery charges up.
If you're within ten meters or closer, the faster it charges.
Yeah! Uh…
Yeah, I know. So,
If this is us
then that means
we have to get even closer?
You mean we have to get physical?
[Dr. Jang] Well,
it would seem you're more likely to be charged by her
if your mucosae were to be touching.
My…
What?
[mysterious music playing]
-[triumphant music playing] -[applause]
[gasps]
Ugh…
No, I refuse! [gasps softly]
Um… Are you good?
So you're saying
that I have to touch that woman?
[sighs]
And if I don't, then I'll die?
[photographer] Just like the test shoot. Look straight ahead. Keep it natural.
Great! Yeah, hold that pose.
Eyes to the camera, good. This is really working.
Na-min, let's get you moving a little closer to Eun-ho.
Okay, now really gaze into each other's eyes.
Yes, perfect! Very nice.
Hold it there. Turn to face the camera. Beautiful.
Hold that pose. We'll take a few more. Yeah, that's great.
The camera loves you. Keep it up. Keep it up!
Cross one leg over the other.
Yeah, this is great. I love it. Very, very suave.
Okay, here we go! That expression is perfect.
Now tilt your head slightly. Nice. Really nice. Hold it there. Yes!
[camera shutter clicking]
Hey, do I have anything else booked today?
You have the overnight shoot. You're not going anywhere.
-[Eun-ho sighs] -Hello, Mr. Ji Eun-ho.
Oh, I'll take that for you, thanks.
Hanlim… Advertising?
Oh. I'm Ma Hee-chan, his manager.
I'm here to make your client an exceptional offer.
Sir, I would love to speak with you in private.
Would that be all right with you?
Oh my gosh! Ah!
Yikes. Why are you creeping around?
Miss Bo-bae.
What? Spit it out.
-[gasps] -I've been giving this a lot of thought.
What do you want?
I've realized something.
Over the past few days, I've been unspeakably rude to you.
What are you…
Wait, are you buttering me up because you need a charge?
Why are you acting so nice?
I just
wanted to say
I feel terrible.
Oh. You do?
Well, that's really nice to know.
[gentle music playing]
[Ho-rang] So?
Will you forgive me for being unspeakably rude?
[heartbeat pounding]
[Bo-bae] I've never been this close to someone before.
[Ho-rang] Tell me,
am I forgiven?
Uh, well,
I guess so.
[gasps]
[sighs] Wonderful.
Now that we respect each other…
[sighs]
…let's draw up a contract.
-[record scratch] -What are you…
To celebrate its 30th anniversary, TS Resort is looking for a fresh new face.
We'd like you to be the ambassador for our brand.
Meaning you would be the new face of TS Group.
A provisional contract.
It's a one-year term with a generous signing bonus.
Oh. Wait.
I think they wrote this wrong. There are way too many zeroes here.
[chuckles softly]
It's right, I promise you.
TS values you, and that number shows they're serious.
But there's always room for negotiation.
You're a major star. It's time you were moving up.
[papers rustling]
A legally binding contract for three months,
which includes a touching provision between us.
[Bo-bae hesitating]
-Wait. Touching what? -Provision.
Non-romantic skin-to-skin contact. All platonic.
[curious music playing]
So, what…
Uh, I have a couple of questions…
Yeah. Sure, ask me anything. [inhales sharply]
Is it possible you have
brain damage?
[Ho-rang hesitates, sighs]
Nope. My brain's okay.
It's not though. Look at your eyes. You've got the crazy eyes.
So am I to understand you don't wanna be my in-charge?
Do I look like I do?
[chuckles]
[chuckles sarcastically]
[laughing]
[laughter continues through gritted teeth]
[Bo-bae sighs]
Hey, Mr. Businessman, you call that a pitch?
-Ha! -[music fades]
[Eun-ho] I can't, I'm sorry.
No matter how much you're offering, I'm not interested in doing ads.
I'm a serious actor, I don't want to be known for commercials.
I believe that in order to be taken seriously, you have to do it all.
A jack-of-all-trades. A perfect actor.
Right…
I don't want your kind of perfection.
I'm more than happy to excel by being the best version of who I am right now.
-[disbelieving chuckle] -[driver] Congratulations, ma'am.
What for?
I thought the smile was because you landed the contract.
Oh… Not quite yet, no.
But it is funny.
He's nothing more than a pretty face,
and yet he still manages to be completely full of himself.
I hoped to come back with the best present Mr. Baek's ever gotten,
but… thanks anyway.
-[woman] Enjoy your meal, sir. -Thank you very much.
Sorry, excuse me.
Do I get my meal soon? I'm so hungry, I'm starving.
Have you passed gas?
I'm only supposed to feed you after you've passed gas.
Ah… No, nothing yet.
That's not true.
What?
-[whimsical music playing] -But I haven't yet.
You did. Early this morning.
Poof.
[Bo-bae snoring]
-[loud snore] -[Ho-rang gasps]
-[snoring continues] -[sighs]
[snoring continues]
Would you mind--
[Bo-bae farts loudly]
[snoring resumes]
[server] Oh, wonderful, you passed gas!
I'll let the nurse know right away. She'll bring you your meal.
[Bo-bae chuckles awkwardly]
[clears throat]
Wow, so I did it, huh? That's good…
I thought your bed was gonna collapse it was so loud.
Be careful out there.
[chuckles] Watch your fart…
Heart!
[Ho-rang slurps]
Ah!
The sound of silence.
[music stops]
Ugh. So embarrassing!
Why? It's perfectly natural.
It means my body is working well.
Oh no, I hate it!
[whimpers, sighs]
[Eun-ho] What do you hate?
Eun-ho.
[both chuckle]
[sighs]
[chuckles]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Mr. Baek.
[footsteps approaching]
The chairwoman told me what happened.
Since we're business partners now, I thought I should visit.
Though she didn't say what the surgery was for?
Uh, appendicitis.
But the doctor told me I wasn't supposed to have visitors yet.
[Seol-hee chuckles]
I wasn't planning on staying too long.
When I heard you were here, I made the trip to see you.
-I'll walk you out. -Oh, no need. I just got here.
I'll only stay a few minutes, since you're not feeling well.
You're so busy You shouldn't be trapped in the hospital.
Uh… [sighs]
[Seol-hee] Hm.
-You feeling any better yet? -Mm-hmm.
Uh, should you even be here right now?
It's like you don't even know you're famous!
So what if I am? I can't visit a friend in hospital?
Uh… [chuckles softly]
Are you sure everything's okay though?
You're pale and awfully thin.
[jaunty music playing]
Yeah?
Mm.
No, I'm all right. I'm not sick.
It's just that
I'm still not really eating.
Just a bit stressed.
What? Who's stressing you out?
You're a bit flushed, too, now I'm really looking at you.
You sure you okay?
[Bo-bae] Obviously I'm flushed. Your gorgeous face is inches away.
[Eun-ho] Is it Director Yeom Min-kyu?
[Bo-bae] Yeah, him. Not just him…
Ugh, thanks for the reminder. Now I'm really stressed.
He told me I only had three months to rework the romance.
[Eun-ho] Like he's an expert on romance. He doesn't know what he's talking about.
I think everything you write is great.
You would, because you're my fan.
No matter what I write, you always say it's great.
Oh no, what am I gonna do?
Oh, that romance is killing me!
If you wanted, I could, uh…
-[clears throat] -[gentle music playing]
…I could help you with the romantic stuff.
Wha…
Well, how are you planning on helping me with all that?
Uh, I mean…
I'm an actor, that's all…
Mr. Baek?
-Do you know those guests? -I don't.
I don't know that woman.
[Bo-bae] But his true identity's shrouded in all this mystery.
He could be the son of a rival boss or…
-[Yeom] Na Bo-bae the writer? -Mm-hmm.
Yeah, she's new. I'm working with her.
Three months left on her contract.
Hey, stop wasting time! That won't be in the shot.
And what about her script? The romance elements, how are they?
Ah, they're weak.
I told her to go out and date someone for inspiration.
I'm surprised you're interested in her work.
-Right, thanks. Take care. -Baek Ho-rang!
What?
Hmm… hmm.
[purposeful music playing]
If someone was standing right in front of me,
practically begging me to ask what's wrong, I'd wanna know.
So that's what she wants.
She's so desperate to fix her sad little script
that she'll put the moves on anyone.
[chuckling]
I bet the two of us can strike a deal.
[music fades]
-[Seol-hee] Do you know those guests? -I don't.
I don't know that woman.
[Bo-bae] The male lead ends up becoming a bodyguard,
but his true identity's shrouded in all this mystery.
He said, "I don't know that woman."
Why did he single her out?
[chuckles softly]
[sighs]
[electricity sizzling]
[music fades]
[screams, gasps]
Is that Na Bo-bae, the writer?
[calming music playing]
What?
Why are you… What are you doing here?
You scared me! I almost passed out! Ugh, my stomach…
You won the top prize at the NBS Drama contest
and debuted with the drama Wistful Youth.
For three years, you've been working on a romance miniseries
with the director Yeom Min-kyu.
Did you run a background check on me?
But the romance is weak, and you're not making progress.
You have three months until your contracts over.
Well, my romance series is none of your business.
[chuckles smugly]
The guy you were talking to outside before, is he your boyfriend?
No. We're just… We're really good friends.
Oh, yeah?
Right.
I'm sure you've noticed that, objectively speaking, I'm quite the catch.
I've got looks, money, social status, personality…
[Bo-bae scoffs]
What's so funny?
I mean, I'll admit you have most of that,
but it's not a winning personality.
On the contrary, wherever I go, I get noticed.
People see me as a true gentleman with impeccable manners.
Impeccable manners, wow…
Ah.
[Ho-rang scoffs] Anyway, I'm used to getting attention.
I'm used to being hit on.
But work keeps me busy, plus with my heart issues,
I don't do long-term relationships.
-You sound so proud. -I am.
I'm trying to impress you here. When it comes to romance, I'm your guy.
Hm. I have a new offer.
If you commit to the contract for three months,
I'll teach you about romance, since you need the help.
And then you can fix your writing.
Do we have a deal?
[music fades]
[footsteps padding]
[Ho-rang breathes deeply]
[curious music playing]
Na Bo-bae?
Sir?
[music fades]
What? What?
[Yang] Never mind.
-[groans] -I brought the documents you requested.
[Ho-rang] Mmm.
[sighs]
You awake over there?
You said you'd think about it. Do you have your answer?
I know you can't still be sleeping. I can hear you breathing from here.
-Pull the curtain. -Sir.
She's not here. But she left something.
[Bo-bae] Emergency Charging Station.
-58-1 Songan-dong, Geumjin-gu, Seoul. -A note.
[Bo-bae] Don't show up unless you're really about to die.
What? "Emergency Charging Station"?
[sighs]
Was I wrong to leave him behind? He does have a heart condition…
[clicks tongue]
Oh, whatever. He has my address, it's fine.
It's not like I didn't try to help him. I really did.
-Okay. -[typing]
“I-hyeok leans in
and buckles Hye-ju's seatbelt…”
[whimsical music playing]
You have to put on your seatbelt, please, ma'am.
[whining] I don't feel like it, no.
-[seat belt unbuckles] -[door opens]
I-HYEOK GETS OUT OF THE CAR AND OPENS THE BACK DOOR.
[secretly pleased] What's wrong?
-You want me to do it for you? -[flustered] What?
[seat belt buckles]
I-HYEOK CUPS HYE-JU'S CHEEK
What else do you want?
[sweeping romantic music playing]
HYE-JU LOOKS AT HIM, NERVOUS
[music becomes uneasy]
I told you, when it comes to romance, I'm your guy.
Now how about we celebrate with a little skin-on-skin?
[frustrated groan]
Ugh! He's even in my scripts! And what was he talking about before?
He'll date me in exchange for physical contact?
Ugh, he's completely nuts!
Besides, the doctor told us
being in close proximity would charge the battery.
"Touching provision," gross! That ass!
[yelling frustratedly]
-Ugh! He's a jerk! He's crazy! -[Ji-hye sighs]
She must be in so much pain.
[gasping emotionally]
Oh no, our poor sweet sis.
[music fades]
Are you sure you're fine to start working again?
Oh yeah, the hospital said that it was all right.
It looked like you were in a lot of pain before.
[Ji-hye sighs]
[pop ballad playing]
What is he doing here?
♪ I know who you are… ♪
Set me up near that woman.
[Yang] Yes. Here's the closest table.
What?
♪ Don't hesitate No matter what you had planned for ♪
♪ We got to move on now ♪
♪ Oh, isn't it right To be who we should be? ♪
♪ Don't say it's just a metaphor ♪
♪ I'm turning pages Of stories only meant for us ♪
♪ We gotta make it ♪
♪ Until we see this journey end… ♪
♪ I know what you're ready… ♪
Everything's ready for you.
♪ Been waiting to let you down ♪
♪ Only thing I meant to say It's only you and me ♪
♪ Can't you see This story is all meant for… ♪
What do you think you're doing?
Getting acquainted with my new office.
We would like to rent this table starting now.
-Two million won enough? -[Ji-hye gasps]
Two million won?
No, thanks. I'll have to ask you to leave--
Two million it is. Welcome, sir.
We hope you enjoy your personal workspace here.
Zip it.
♪ Turning pages Of stories only meant… ♪
But…
♪ We gotta make it… ♪
Get to work.
♪ …until this journey ends ♪
♪ I know what you're ready to die for… ♪
-Good night. Thanks a lot. -See you next time.
♪ Only thing I meant to say It's only you and me ♪
♪ Can't you see This story is all meant for love ♪
[loud squeak]
[sighs] We're closing for the night, sir, if you please.
My stuff can stay where it is because we'll be back tomorrow.
Hey!
Are you actually planning to sit there every day for three months?
I said… [hesitates]
Look, I said… [whispers] this is an emergency charging station.
"Emergency." You know what that means?
I deal with emergencies every day.
And you still haven't given me your answer.
Trading touch for romance.
Think on it. I'll wait.
Tomorrow, I'll ask again.
[lively music playing]
[Bo-bae sighs]
[door opens, closes]
[groans]
[frustrated whining]
Your drinks are ready.
[loud click]
[chimes tinkling]
Thank you, sir.
[watch chimes]
[lively music continues]
[sighs]
[music fades]
You have to stop coming here.
You're the one who gave me the address. You told me where I could find you.
The note specifically said only come here if you're actually dying.
[Ho-rang] That's the thing.
The second you leave my side, I feel like I'm dying.
[romantic music playing]
This is the only place we can be together, and that's hard enough.
I just wanna be around you.
Oh my God…
[Ho-rang] Say I can stay.
[music stops]
Just let me stay by your side.
[sighs] Fine, you win.
Huh?
-Come here. -[Bo-bae] Why?
Just come on.
[Bo-bae sighs]
Huh?
-What? -Stop.
You keep trying to kick that customer out. What's wrong with you?
The cafe's been busy since he started showing up.
We were doing just fine without his help, I'm sure.
"Just fine" is miles away from "busy," isn't it?
Also, how did you even meet him?
He's so incredibly handsome. He looks superrich too.
Well… He's just someone from the hospital. We met there.
Does he like you? What about the shocks?
-Does he not know about that yet? -[sighs]
You have to get your electric stuff under control if you two--
It's not like that. I don't wanna talk about it.
[jaunty music playing]
-Ugh! -Uh-uh.
Ugh, what now?
Don't you dare go talk to him again.
Come on.
[Bo-bae groans]
[sighs]
[calming music playing]
[exhales slowly]
[watch chimes]
-[inhales deeply, sighs heavily] -[music fades]
[mischievous music playing]
The charge,
what's making it drain so fast?
[music continues]
[Ho-rang groans]
How long has it been since I was discharged?
Exactly one week, sir.
The longest week of my life. This is ridiculous.
How do I last three months?
The time will fly by. You'll just have to be patient.
I've been polite and I've smiled, and that smile always works.
But it doesn't work on her. [groans]
Maybe she can't get past your initial impression.
You were pretty rude. I can't really blame her.
I wasn't that bad.
Besides, even if you two got along perfectly,
it would be hard to spend the whole day together.
Living in separate houses.
Separate… houses?
[cell phone buzzing]
[Ho-rang sighs]
Yes, Grandma?
Yes. I'll be there soon.
All right.
We'll go to the resort, then to Pyeonchang-dong.
Maybe we should see Miss Bo-bae first. Don't you need a charge?
I'll just take care of this nice and quick.
[contemplative music playing]
[music fades]
Hey, I thought you had plans in Sangam tonight.
-Shouldn't you be heading out? -Oh yeah, look at the time.
-[Ji-hye] Writers' meeting, right? -Uh-huh.
With old classmates from the drama academy. See you later.
-Okay, have fun. -[Bo-bae] Oh, and just in case, uh…
Forget it. [chuckles] Bye-bye.
Bye.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[Ho-rang sighs]
Ho-rang. Why the long face? Got some bad news to share?
No, I've just got a lot on my mind.
I'm disappointed you can't complete your work during business hours.
I wasn't doing work, I was checking the time.
So bored of us already, are you?
Mom, my son Do-yoon prioritizes family and does excellent work.
Remember, how he organized TS Hotel's 30th anniversary event?
And he did it all without complaint. Tirelessly.
-He was buzzing all over like a busy bee. -I was? Really?
Shut up.
The busy bee certainly succeeded in humiliating our company.
[aunt] Oh, Mom…
You can't listen to those articles. It was practically a peck on the cheek.
-That's all it was. -Don't you condone his behavior!
[grandma] Good thing I had the money to cover it up.
But I don't enjoy burying incidents of sexual harassment.
Ow! Oh, that's hot!
The staff should not be serving it this hot!
It's hot.
Grandmother, the thing is,
that night got blown out of proportion.
I was just having fun at the club. In fact, I was actually there for work.
Social media's a big deal right now.
If you get a lot of followers, you're called an "influencer"--
You assume I don't know what an influencer is?
Wow, our chairwoman's so smart.
Ho-rang,
I understand you did an excellent job with the Jeju Resort.
[Ho-rang] It went well. It should help with our rebranding.
All we need is to find the perfect new face.
Once we have, I expect the brand's value will more than triple.
Maybe more, if you marry the daughter of Hanlim Advertising Company.
-But you're dragging your feet. -[aunt] Mom!
Just set her up with my son, Do-yoon. Please, Ho-rang doesn't even want her!
Keep your voice down. You're scaring Bokdeongi.
[tense music playing]
Running off to a secret girlfriend?
You practically ran outta there.
[Ho-rang sighs]
I can't stay. I don't have time to deal with you.
You were looking at your watch all through dinner. Is something going on?
What do you care anyway? It's none of your concern.
-And I don't have to explain myself. -[scoffs]
Why don't you go kiss up to Grandma?
Tell her what an influencer is. She loved that one.
If only our grandmother knew how much of a prick you are.
[tires screech]
[uneasy music playing]
-Where's Miss Bo-bae? -She had plans. Out with friends--
Where did she go?
Why do you wanna know?
[Ho-rang breathes heavily]
I need to see her immediately. Can't you just tell me where she went?
[woman 1] Ju-hee, you're about to start shooting, right?
Mm-hmm, yeah.
[woman 1] Mm.
Get this, the two stars are Kim Hae-ri and Kang Jun
and the director is Yeom Min-kyu.
[woman 1] Wow, that's amazing! It's gonna be huge, I just know it!
[Ju-hee] I hope so.
NBS is promoting it as one of their most anticipated shows. [chuckles]
Bo-bae, what about you?
Huh?
[clears throat, coughs] What?
[Ju-hee] It's been forever since we saw you. How've you been?
Every time we talk, you just say you're writing.
So what are you working on?
Hmm… It's, um… [clears throat]
Mm…
Uh, well, I'm currently working with Yeom Min-kyu too.
Yeah, we'll probably start production once they're wrapped your show.
Wait, you're writing Director Yeom's next project?
Are you kidding, girl? Wow, that's so great! Congratulations!
They've already found the male lead. It's Ji Eun-ho. You know who he is?
Ji Eun-ho? You kidding? I'm a big fan! [gasps excitedly]
[Bo-bae] Really? He's actually a good friend.
He's been begging me to finish the script for my show
the male lead so bad.
So that's exciting. Ji Eun-ho is all set to star.
[woman 2 chuckles]
Ji Eun-ho's, like, a big deal. Does he have time for your show?
Didn't he make you that promise when he was just starting out?
I don't think so. I met up with him a few days ago
and he still seemed interested in the script.
Even if all I was doing was complaining about how stressed I was.
It's just that
you really shouldn't blindly trust whatever an actor says.
Ji Eun-ho… He's probably booked years in advance.
He has a busy schedule. He can't work on just anything.
Especially for a writer who's barely made a name for herself.
Oh yeah, you're right. That's true.
"Barely made a name for herself," what am I saying? [inhales sharply]
It's not like she's had a hit yet.
Maybe one day.
[pensive music playing]
Hey, guys, If somebody at this table hasn't made it yet, it's me, not Bo-bae.
She's already debuted her work.
[Ju-hee] Right. Of course.
I forgot. So she did.
Oh, I was only looking out for our friend.
[women giggle]
[K-indie music playing]
[Ju-hee] Imagine if the actor flakes on her. That would be terrible.
-I couldn't let that happen to Bo-bae. -Hey, you.
[Bo-bae gasps]
-[Ju-hee gasps] -Ji Eun-ho!
[coughs]
Oh, hi.
I was just passing by after dinner and saw you.
Sorry, you're with your friends.
[women chuckle]
Uh… No worries. Hello…
[giggling]
Yes, we all went to drama school together.
-Ah, so then you're all writers? -We are.
You know, it's funny. We were just talking about you.
[Korean ballad playing]
[Eun-ho] Hey…
They were good things, I hope?
Oh yeah, of course, yeah. [giggles]
If you're almost done, I can take you home.
I'll be heading your way.
-Uh… -No, I don't think we're quite done.
Oh, come on… This is so cute! My gosh!
-Oh, we gotta let them go! Ah! Yeah! -Go now!
[woman 1] She's good. Go!
Shall we?
-Your bag. -Oh!
[woman 1] Get home safe, girlfriend! Bye!
-Great meeting you. [giggles] -Same.
-Yeah. Almost felt like we summoned you. -[music fades]
One minute we were talking about you. The next--
[sighs] Saved you from a fate worse than death?
You didn't overhear anything, did you?
Well… maybe a bit of the last part.
[Bo-bae sighs]
You told me her name, Ju-hee?
She's the one who wouldn't stop bullying you?
I gotta say, you undersold her. She was even worse than your stories.
She takes "stink eye" to a whole new level. Whoa!
[chuckling]
We all started writing at the same time, but I'm the only one still here.
Kinda pathetic…
Why do you say that?
I think your writing's incredible.
[gentle music playing]
Seriously, I became an actor because of you.
"Yes, it's true."
"Studying for the civil service exam at my age is embarrassing."
"But you can't give up! It's not time to."
"You can't give up. It's not time to…"
"You can't give up. It's not time to!"
"You…"
[whispers] "You can't give up."
Sorry everyone. Sorry.
[Yeom] Eun-ho…
Is this a cold read? Have you ever read this script before out loud?
I'm sorry, sir.
[Yeom] Okay… Just relax. It's only one episode.
If we wanna get out of here before dark, we have to get through it.
-Truly sorry. Excuse me. -[Yeom] Let's start from the top.
[music fades]
Oh, hello.
[sighs] I'm sorry for messing up your script.
Wait, hang on…
It… It's just you shouldn't be sorry.
You didn't do anything wrong. You were so in character.
Watching you, I thought, "Oh, okay, so he's more like this. Got it."
[Bo-bae chuckles]
I wrote the words, but you brought them to life.
Thank you for that. Truly.
-You took it seriously. -No, I should be thanking you--
-No, I'm thanking you. -No, thank you, really.
-No, I'm serious, thank-- -No.
-I gotta thank you! -Thank you so much.
[Eun-ho] I've been your number-one fan ever since.
What I'm trying to say
is it doesn't really matter what they think of you.
You deserve better. Don't beat yourself up.
Mm-hmm. [chuckles]
[Ji-hye] She said she was going to Sangam to meet up with some friends,
and then head straight home after.
-[uneasy music playing] -[breathing shakily]
[brakes squealing]
[music stops]
Okay, bye! Thanks again.
[wistful music playing]
WISHING THE GREATEST DAY TO THE GREATEST ACTOR
[Bo-bae] You've done so much for me.
A CITY BURSTING WITH CHARM: THIS IS THE HEART OF SEOUL
[Bo-bae] But it's hard not to wonder…
Everyone in this city is always moving forward,
getting better.
But I'm just stuck.
No hit shows, no fame, no talent…
But I act like I'm just as good as them.
I pretend I'm doing great, but who am I kidding?
That's all I do. Pretend, pretend, pretend.
Why is everyone moving onto bigger things and leaving me behind?
I wanna go too… [sighs]
[uneasy music playing]
[dramatic unsettling music playing]
[screams]
-[music fades] -[man groans]
[Kang-ho breathes heavily]
Get outta here.
[footsteps recede]
[hesitates] Mr. Baek, what are you… what are you doing here?
[gasps]
[romantic music playing]
[watch chimes]
[Ho-rang sighing]
Miss Bo-bae, I… I can't lie anymore.
[Bo-bae] Huh?
[Ho-rang] My plan was to make sure you saw me every day.
And that way, I might be able to win you over.
[Bo-bae] What're you talking about?
Get… Stop it, get off me. Oh.
[Ho-rang sighs] But I can't wait.
[Ho-rang pants]
I can't take it slow.
I can't live without you.
If anything were to happen to you, I…
[breathes shakily]
…I would die.
I'll do anything you ask of me. Whatever you need for your script.
If you want,
I can even be romantic.
Dinners, flowers, all that.
Come live with me.
We'll only touch as much as you're comfortable.
I don't need much contact. We can just hold hands.
Hang on, wait, wait… Back up. I'm pretty sure you just said…
I'm…
Did I hear that right? You want me to move in?
Yes. Today made things very clear.
I won't waste time searching the back alleys of Seoul for you
in a life-or-death situation.
Imagine if the worst had happened.
How exactly am I supposed to recharge without you?
Please, Miss Bo-bae.
I need you by my side.
[Ho-rang sighs]
Ah…
Hang on, this whole time you were talking about recharging?
[watch chimes]
[chimes]
-[Korean ballad playing] -[Bo-bae gasps]
Oh my gosh.
This is…
It's like an ultimate charge… But only when we touching?
Ultimate charge? Yeah.
That is a good way to say it.
The battery charges faster the more intense the touch is.
What? That's impossible. Uh…
[gasps]
Please save me, Na Bo-bae.
-[Korean ballad playing] -Until the surgery. Just for three months.
Recharge my heart.
[Yeom] You've got three months.
Three months to cook up a steamy romance. I'm counting on you.
You're on.
I'll do it.
Your heart's safe with me.
[music intensifies]
[watch chimes]
[rhythmic chiming]
[Korean ballad continues]
[music fades out]